William Neil Smith papers, 1829-1975 (Bulk 1944-1970)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Audio-Visual Media, 1922-1974
  - Sound Recordings
    - Other Native and Spanish recordings -- 7 inch reels. (Box 35)
      Haitian rhythms, Spanish music, miscellaneous. Side 1: track 1) Haitian music, 2) Mexican music "La Bamba," 3) Spanish music. Side 2: track 1) Spanish music, 2) Music of the Danube (Hungarian, Romanian, and Viennese), 3) The Blue Danube (J. Strauss Jr.), and 4) Pizzicato Polka (J. Strauss) [Tales of the Vienna Woods finale]. No date
      Spanish music, miscellaneous. No date
    - Recordings -- reel to reel. 1956-1958 (Box 35A)
      I-VI Lidia Ibarra (Seri girl) puberty ceremony (songs and foot drum). Desemboque, Sonora. June 10-13, 1958
      VII Tarahumara music. Alta Taraheu (licensed by W. Disney). summer 1956
      VIII Mestizo and Anglos of Panalachi, Chihuahua music. Mountains of southwest Chihuahua, Rio Concho, and Village of Panalachi. June 1956
    - Seri recordings -- on disks. 1944-1952 (Box 36)
      Seri at Kino Bay, Sonora, [one 12 inch disk]. ca. 1944-1945
      Jesus Montaño (Seri man), songs - recorded at Tucson, [one 12 inch disk]. September 29, 1948
      Seri trip to States, Interview with Ben Slack, KVOA, Tucson [two 12 inch disks]. October 6, 1948
      Seri trip to States, Interview with Ben Slack, Town Crier program, KVOA, Tucson [two 10 inch disks]. October 17, 1952
      "Mexican Indian music - audition" [Seri?], [one 7 inch disk]. No date
- Series VII: Supplemental Material, 1950-1960
  - Miscellaneous lecture posters, display cards. ca. 1950s-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Sketches of Seri designs and objects. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Pencil sketch: "Seri shrine, Kino Bay," by H. Arden Edwards. 1950 (Box 37, Folder 3)